Suddenly Explorers! Suddenly Explorers!
Star's Stone of a plain, plain child! Please take care of Karen Tachibana and her friends from Ikinari Talk!
Please take care of us! We are the Ikinari Expedition!
Today we have Ms. Karen!
Karen, is that you? Do you like animals?
I love animals so much!
Lately, I spend all my free time watching animal videos that make me feel soft and fuzzy.
I'm still busy taking care of my cats on my smartphone app.
What do you mean you've been busy taking care of them?
You're doing it on your own because it's an app.
It's an app.
That's how much?
All kinds of cats?
Yes, that's right.
Lately, as I've gotten older.
I'm getting more and more comfortable with animals.
I'm just trying to get to know them better.
Hand-to-mouth?
I don't take care of them.
It's easy to write, but
You've become a "muzugoro", haven't you?
I'm sure you've been busy with work lately, so I thought I'd heal Karen with animals.
So today, I thought I'd try to soothe Karen's soul with an animal... and today's exploration is this way.
Let's get in touch with animals!
I'm so happy!
On the first floor of E-BINS, the pet store Ricky has just opened.
We haven't been there yet, so today we'd like to introduce you to Karen, who loves animals.
Today, I'd like to send Karen, who loves animals, over there to explore. It's basically a pet store, but you can touch and feel the animals.
Let's move on to the store.
Yes, we've arrived.
We've arrived.
You can see a glimpse of it.
It's like a genre.
Animal Park.
You hear all kinds of voices.
So let's go inside for a bit.
Let's get to know each other.
Are you sure?
Then let's go.
I'm looking forward to it.
Excuse me for interrupting.
Let's get out of the way.
First zone.
Chinchilla.
Chinchillas.
Are you feeling sick?
Too cute!
I've never seen so many different kinds of people.
I didn't know there were beetles.
What about this one?
Ferret.
A ferret.
He's so cute!
It's a very loving ferret.
It's true.
They love to play.
Can I touch them?
Is that okay?
But he's sleeping.
It's okay.
Yeah, it's okay.
It's warm! It's sticky.
He's so spaced out.
Can I get the same look?
You're making the same face.
Can you actually touch it?
If you like it, you can buy it?
I see.
I want to take it home with me.
Buy it.
At least buy it.
It's cute.
Thank you very much.
I'm thirsty.
It's warm.
What did you do?
Oh, shit.
Is it a girl or a boy?
A boy.
What did you do?
My hand.
Lingering?
Warmth.
It's still warm.
I'm holding something.
He's so cute. He's so cute.
Hamster.
Hamsters OK?
This one bites, so if you wear a blog...
He's wearing it.
Cheers.
Sorry, this is my first one.
Embarrassing.
Cute.
Amazing.
엔 2 or 4
So cute!
He's squirming.
He's doing it.
His whiskers are moving so much!
It's moving.
So cute!
They've been playing a hamster game lately.
You know...
There's a stuffed animal.
It's cute. It looks just like that one.
What do you think?
They're so cute!
I really want to pick them all up.
He's so cute!
This cute little hamster is right next to them.
Oni Plate Lizard
Oni Plate Lizards?
Oni Plate Lizards are so cool with their rugged armor-like scales.
These are so cute!
Can I touch it?
I can touch them without gloves.
Without gloves?
You're going? Kane-san is taking off his gloves like he's taking a bath.
Of course I want to touch you.
Your belly.
Yes, sir.
My belly is pudgy.
You have a flabby belly?
Flat belly.
He's cute.
He doesn't gobble?
He doesn't gobble.
He looks at me so much.
You're really keeping an eye on him, aren't you?
Yeah, he does.
It's so rugged.
It's rugged?
On the surface.
Is he pudgy?
That's an old man.
Is there a male or female?
She's just unknown.
Unknown.
You're not sure?
I don't know.
That's amazing.
Can I keep her, too?
Yes, I can.
What should I feed him?
Meat, roast chicken...
We'll buy it.
Let's buy some.
I see.
Is there an initial set or something?
You do?
Then, if you decide you want to keep him...
You'll have to do it yourself, Mom.
I see.
We can make a lot of things for each other.
What?
Just now.
Panda mouse.
I heard about that.
I heard there was a mouse the size of your thumb.
Tiny.
Really cute.
Cute
Tiny
Panda glass
Panda and
Cute.
It's a panda.
I like the color.
I think I want to put it in black and white.
I have to.
Wow.
He's so cute.
It's so tiny.
Oh, my God.
Oh, no!
So cute.
It's so small!
The size in drops
Not much more
Heh.
They're cute.
Average weight 5.15 grams.
I hear they're easy to care for.
Oh, wow.
They're very friendly.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
What should we name him? If I were to buy one, I'd name it.
If we name him, he'll take it home with him.
What should we do? Mr. Pan?
Mr. Bread? Don't name him something like Orauta.
Oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God.
I thought Japan was a cow, too, color-wise.
I'm so pulled in by the cow.
You know what?
Willpower and pride.
Pla, pla, pla.
Pla-kun?
Jid Pride, Kana-san was the idol Jid Pride.
Even Iri-chan is that, so, Pla, Pla of Pride
You make me carry a lot of weight, the song.
That's true.
Pla-chan... right?
You're so cute, aren't you?
This angle, this angle is cute.
Oh, it's so cute!
So cute!
I can stare at it forever.
Oh, my God.
You wanna come over?
You coming?
Pura-chan's big adventure is about to begin.
Can you help me?
Thank you very much.
I don't think she's coming.
He's really cute.
I'm so happy.
It's just the beginning.
You'll get to know a lot of them in this early stage.
There are so many different kinds of pets.
It's not like a regular pet store.
I'm not talking about a regular pet store, but a regular petting zoo.
You know, like a dog-only area.
or cats only.
This place has a really wide range of
Cute!
I'm looking at them.
This early on.
Cute.
Thank you for watching.
So cute.
Look at that, folks.
I'm calling it.
Hello.
Oh, my God.
Kiyoko.
It's Kiyoko.
She's cute.
Cute.
Fluffy.
He's so quiet.
He's a good boy.
Oh, my God.
Is this what it looks like?
I thought I saw it, but it's real.
Oh, my God.
Is it real?
It's moving.
It moves when you bend it.
It's moving like crazy.
Excuse me, excuse me.
He's so cute and moist.
She looks like Yutaka Oe.
The enka singer.
I see.
How is it? The texture.
Like silk.
Soft.
Soft and fluffy.
It's like touching cotton wool.
It's like you're not touching it.
You can touch an owl? That's amazing.
It's amazing.
Okay, then,
I'd like to go to the main event,
This way.
What's this?
What's the name?
Mine Event.
Anaconda.
Anaconda?
It says "yellow anaconda.
This one?
Yes, sir.
That's not a heavy guy.
That's not a werecat.
Wait a minute, can you touch this?
This one.
You can wrap it around your neck.
You know what they say.
It says you can wrap it around your neck.
It's written like a scarf.
I'm interested. I'm interested.
I'm interested.
Is this okay?
I've tried it. Are you doing it at home?
Are you doing it at home?
Explanation
It weighs about 10 kg, so it's heavy.
Whole body muscles.
Amazing.
Yum!
Thank you.
Please.
The bag is a mess.
It's really heavy.
Oh, my God.
The skin is pretty plump and cute
It's amazing!
It's so pretty.
Are you okay?
Yeah, it's fine.
Is it cool?
It's cool.
It's good for summer.
It's not good for summer.
It's not like a summer stole or anything.
It's cute.
I love it.
Where do you put it?
He's perched on my elbow.
It's a great picture, but...
I can pet it so much.
He really has ears.
They're the size of a school bag.
It's like a metaphor.
Wow, it's really powerful!
Yes, it is.
So thick!
Especially plump.
He's staring at me.
My brother in black is staring at me.
Good night, sir.
You! Like...
You're insane! Like that.
You can't wrap it around the bag.
Yes, yes, yes.
So it's a salad.
That's a rare experience, isn't it?
It's your first time, isn't it?
I'm so excited.
There's no "ah-ha" or "ah-ha"? Reaction.
You're even cuter than I thought you'd be, and you fit right in.
Yes, I did.
You've got a strawberry on you.
But the bag surprises me the most.
So cute!
Thank you so much.
Thank you very much.
Doggy corner.
Excuse me.
Kumicon is amazing.
Oh, my God.
A puppy.
Isn't it rare to meet a puppy?
Of course it is.
They're so tiny.
You can buy them at pet stores.
They say it's a small package.
I've always had cat skin.
I've always had a soft spot for cats, but I've come to realize how cute Wai-chan is.
I'm trying to live with Wai-chan and the cat in my old age
I'm living now.
You're already thinking about retirement?
So many pretty flowers!
What a surprise!
I thought it was a gargal, with a nose.
I almost sat down.
The face is...
Oh, my God, I want one of these puzzles.
I want all these puzzles.
Including Karen's.
Can you put these puzzles in here?
Can you put them in here?
It's nap time.
Hi, sweetie.
He's so cute.
I'm so happy for you.
I'm glad you miss him, too.
He misses his idol and his uncle equally.
They're good kids, aren't they?
They sure come to all of us.
Sit down with Karen or me and see which one you come to.
No, no, no, no, don't be fooled.
No, no, no, no, you don't understand.
Yes, you do.
You don't know what laughter is.
That's what you just called me.
You just called me with your hand.
I'm not going.
It's better this way.
Come here.
Come here. Come here.
Come on.
It's a little long.
He's on his knees.
If we don't get this off him, we're gonna lose him.
That's the end of the scoring cycle.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
She's cute, too.
Sleep.
Sleeping.
He found the best position for himself.
He's so cute.
It fits.
It's cute.
Cute.
Really scary
Mother, the seven buttons proprietary una knucca
I'm so scared!
Babies and man-cats...
They really do give us pure love, don't they?
Yes, they do.
That's what's really stuck with me lately.
What's with this documentary-like comment?
It's like you're a person without a shadow of a doubt!
What a sudden poem!
Scary!
You are sleeping so calmly.
I know, it's so bad!
I can't move.
I can't go home.
Hey, kitty.
They're here.
Here it comes.
Oh, that hurt.
It hurt.
He's so cute.
He's so cute. He's so cute.
So cute.
Cute eyes.
Cute.
Oh, man, this is so cute.
I'm tempted to buy it.
I'm sure you will.
You can really buy it.
First of all, you can buy it.
You'll want to keep it once you've stuffed it with cozy clothes.
They're all snuggled up together.
They must be very calm.
Let it cool down.
They won't do it.
Come on, let's do it together.
Let's do it together.
Oh!
You like seeing this face.
It's true.
So close.
I don't know what I'm gonna do.
I'm so happy.
Thank you so much.
Smile like you're graduating.
The choreography? Before the ballad?
The animals will hold this up for you, so you all have a good night.
Good night.
Thank you very much.
They'll see you all!
I hope you find this girl happy and want to eat her weight!
Please, by all means, look at Mr. Kin-Ginza and try to make contact with him!
This, he touched me with his hand!
So cute!
Majikuru!
Mr. Majikuru!
I didn't think I'd ever see anything like it in Kumasaka!
Really, this is a real life glo